shoppingate.info 2015-03-15

# About Us

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Shoppingate Software.

Shoppingate is a service that designed to help you compare products and prices while you shop online.

Shoppingate is activated only on sites that are listed in our white list. This sites list is updated from time to time.

When you visit a website from our white list, Shoppingate detects the product you are looking for and automatically searchs thousands of vendors for more deals and better price. Alternative prices and other product information will then be displayed.

When you get to one of the site in that list, Shoppingate service sends the product information you are looking for to our servers in order to search for alternatives deals.

All data sent to our servers by the Shoppingate service is anonymous and does not contain any Personally Identifiable Information, like email, name, address etc.

The information sent to our servers is anonymous and may include the IP address, the URL of the web site you are visiting, a general information about your browser and operating system, a product information as taken from the product HTML page and unique identifier of your Shoppingate service.

Shoppingate works with third-party content providers to serve comparative offers. We share the anonymous information with such companies in order to retrieve and present alternative product pricing and information. Shoppingate does not place any restrictions on usage of this anonymous information by its third-party partners.

We do not share any Personally Identifiable Information with any third parties, except if it's required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

Shoppingate uses cookies that enable our servers to recognize and identify your web browser. This information helps us to customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you when using Shoppingate.

While we try to link only to websites that we believe share our respect for privacy, please be aware that Shoppingate is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.

Personal Identifiable Information (PII) Collection: If you choose to contact Shoppingate support in any mean of communication you might be asked to provide the following information: Mandatory information-Contact Name, e-mail, Optional information- Users Company, Phone Number or other personal information which constitute PII under law. Any PII that we collect is stored and processed on servers located in the U.S. and will not be shared with any third parties.

How Your Information is Processed ("Purposes"): The reason for asking the user to provide the above information is to allow the user to send queries and requests to Shoppingate and for Shoppingate representatives (Support/Bizdev) to get those queries and be able to get back to the sender by e-mail or phone.

To Whom Your Information is disclosed: We do not share your PII with any third party. Any processing performed by any Recipients will (where required by law), be governed by a data processing agreement in the form required by law, preserving any and all of your statutory data protection rights and obligating the Recipients to respect the PII and handle it in accordance with the relevant laws.

Security: We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the privacy of your PII. We will make best efforts to ensure that your information will be accessible only by authorized employees of the Company who need to have access to this information in order to provide you with the services on our website. However, you should be aware that there is no data that is transmitted over the Internet that can be guaranteed 100% secure in transmission or safe from theft or illegal capture, and therefore we do not guaranty absolute resistance from unauthorized access.

Contact Us  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email to privacy@Shoppingate.info

This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 30th, 2014.
